http://leatherspinsters.com/privacystatement.html

Privacy Statement for The Leather Spinsters Site
Privacy Statement for The Leather Spinsters Site
St.Mary Publishing Company of Houston has created this privacy statement in order to
demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
The following discloses our
information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: The Leather Spinsters Site.We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server,
and to administer our Web site.
We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests.Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).
The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.
We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.This site contains links to other sites.
The Leather Spinsters Site is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.(*Since you indicated that there are special relationships, such as "Powered by" partners, business partners, cobranded sites, then these relationships must be addressed in your privacy statement.
These relationships need to be clearly defined and it must be clear who is receiving the information collected by the site and who has access to this information.
It must be clear what type of information is shared.
Is only select information shared?
Is the sharing of information limited to only aggregate information?)Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services.
We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).
The customer's contact information is used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).
The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address) and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).
The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site.
These ads may contain cookies.
While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.Public Forums
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users.
Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.Choice/Opt-OutOur site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
You can send email to webmaster@leatherspinsters.comContacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the
practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site,
you can contact
webmaster@leatherspinsters.com
Copyright 1997-2025
